Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Accession #2009.061, 1905-2005; MS2009 Series 18; 3.5 Linear Feet
  - Stanton Park, 1905 June 12 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - FOPP (Friends if Providence Park), 1990, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - KCNTF (Kentucky Courts Neighborhood task force), 1997-2000 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Stawton Park Neighborhood watch network trust fund, undated (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - BEALL, 1997-2001 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Roback Bequest, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - PJDF (Papa Johns Defense Fund), 1998 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Trust Fund - interest digest, 1997-2005 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Trust Fund - General ledger, 2002-2005 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - BSNA (Bryan School Neighborhood Association) CHRS trust fund, 1996-2000 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Call box, trust fund 15004, 2004-2005 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - FOLP (Friends of Lincoln Park), 2000-2001 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - FOMP (Friends of Marion Park), 1993-2000 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - FOMP design, 1995-2000 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - "Party Houses", 1993-1997 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Nuisance property, 1977-1985 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Nuisance property, 2001 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Complaints, 2001-2002 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - CHRS vs DC Board of Zoning adjustment, 2002 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - CHRS vs DC Board of Zoning adjustment petitioner brief, undated (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Zoning committee, 1998-2002 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Zoning committee, 2001 October 18 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Zoning committee, 2000 October 26 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Zoning committee, 2001 June 06 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Zoning committee, 2001 April 26 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Zoning committee, 2001 March 15 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Zoning committee, 2001 November 25 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Campaign against Cooke Stadium, 1993-1995 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - CPC (Community Policy Council), 1995-1996 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Ave. 400 block and area adjacent to S. Capitol stadium, 1991-1998 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Demolotion by neglect, 1990-1998 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Complaint 310 D st NE, 1997 November 24 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Complaint 132 D st NE, 1998-2000 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Complaint 218 11th St. SE, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - 8th and Independence, 1997-1998 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Inquiry 325 7th St., 2000 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Board of Zoning Adjustment appeal no. 16935, binder, 2003 December 07 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Handicapped I ZC 97-15, 1998-2001 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - TDRs, 1999-2000 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Curb cut and appeal, 1997-1998 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - 2 Sixth st. NE, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - 441 5th NE, 1993-1994 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - 16648 300-332 H NE(Amco), 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - 16731 647 Massachusetts NE, 1999-2001 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - 16734 500 D NE, 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - 16755 220 5th St. SE, 2001 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Complaint: 324 Independence, 1998-1999 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - 124 6th St. SE, 1988-1993 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - 16404 (appeal) 434 New Jersey Ave. SE, 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - 16374 405-407 East Capitol, 1998 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - 16373 403 East Capitol SE, 1998 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - 16363 8 Fourth St. SE, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - 16370 434 New Jersey Ave SE, 1998 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Boys Town Pennsylvania and Potomac Ave, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Medlink project, 1992-2000 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Evergreen Baptist church St. James Epescapal church, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Non residential uses in R-4 district, 1986 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Holladay proposal, 2000 August 24 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - 1312 East Capitol St. NE, 1986 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Commission order no. 347 case no.78-12, 1981 July 09 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - 514 Second St. SE R-4 District, 1979-1983 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - 811 C St. SE - 1983, undated (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - 907 Maryland Ave. R-4, 1998 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Carriage Houses, undated (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - 59 Coletta School, 1999-2000 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Zoning committee, 1997-2000 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - 16601 NJ, K, L, & 2nd Sq741, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - 1032 D st. NE 16606, 1999-2000 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - 16607 1201 F NE & 533 12th NE, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - 16608 417 East Capitol, 1977-2000 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - 16622 1022 Maryland Ave, NE, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - 16629 233 Pennsylvania Ave SE, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - FOIA Suit, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Attorney, 2002 (Box 142, Folder 21)
  - Proposal for Survey of buildings in HD, 1995 July (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - FOIA Suit, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Attorney, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Proposal for Survey of buildings in HD, 1995 July (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - 18 3rd St. SE 16423, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - 16445 1324 E St. SE National Graduate University, 1999 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - 16415 1108 3rd St. SE (CAG), 1998 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - 16446 728 F NE, 1999 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - 16466, 1999 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - 16467 1011 Maryland Ave. NE, 1997-1998 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - 16475 403 C St. NE, 1995-1999 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - 16538 407 8th SE, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - BZA 1654 12-16 7th NE, 1999-2000 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - 16547 521 7th SE, 1999-2000 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - 16595 712 East Capitol NE, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - 16658 310 5th St. SE, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - 16670 910 East Capitol NE, 2001 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - 16685 321 4th St. SE, 2000-2001 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - 16689 963 14th SE, 2001 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - 16692 639A NE, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - 16703 308 D St NE, 2001 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - 16709 301 3rd SE, 2000-2001 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - 16712 231 9th SE, 1995-2001 (Box 143, Folder 22)
- Accession #2004.001, 1956-2004; Series 19; 1.5 Linear Feet
  This series includes various documents from a 2004 accession including brocures, maps, pamplets, handouts, correspondence, newsletters, guidelines, directories, meeting minutes, and specific project papers from 1956-2004.
  - "A Snapshot of my Two Years as President of CHRS: 1988-1990" By Pat Schauer, Undated; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, Maps, and Handouts, 1995; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society House Tours - Pamplets and Information, 1959 - 1965; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society House Tour - Pamplet and Information, 1981-1990; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society House Tours - Pamphlets, 1991-1996; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society House Tours - Pamphlets and Information, 1997-2004; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - "Capitol Hill Restoration Society 1997-8 Organizational Handbook" by Patricia Schauer and Gail Lau Kee, 1998; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Symposium, 1985-1991; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Traffic Task Force and Barney Circle, 1983-1993; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - "CHRS House Tour Guidelines" by Patricia Schauer and Edee Hogan, 1998; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 5 (1/3))
  - "CHRS House Tour Guidelines" by Patricia Schauer and Edee Hogan, 1998; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 6 (2/3))
  - "CHRS House Tour Guidelines" by Patricia Schauer and Edee Hogan, 1998; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 7 (3/3))
  - Correspondence about Lee's Funeral Home, 1989; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and Poster on DC Government Integrity Standards, 1989 August - 1990 May; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence about Resignation of Robert Hughes, 1990 January 26-27; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Directory and Meeting Minutes, 1989; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - Documents Concerning 1200 Pennsylvania Ave SE and Shotgun House (both properties owned by Larry Quillian), 1988-1989, 2002; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - Documents Concerning Donations, 1966, Circa 1997; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1990-1991; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - National Children's Island - Development Documents, 1984-1987; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter, 1956-1958; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, 1958-1959; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, 1959-1960; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, 1960-1961; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, 1961-1962; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, 1962-1963; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, 1963-1964; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, 1964-1965; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters, 1965 November-December; Series 19 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter - "News", 1982 September-1985 May; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 16)
  - Newsletter - "News", 1985 June-1988 December; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter - "News", 1989 January-1992 December; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 18)
  - Newsletter - "News", 1993 January-1997 June; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 19)
  - Newsletters - "News", 1997 October - 2000 March; Series 19 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter - "News", 2000 April - 2001 September; Series 19 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters - "News", 2001 October - 2004 July; Series 19 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles from New York Times and Washington's Hill Rag, 1988; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 20)
  - President Stories, 1989-1991; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 21)
  - Prosper Court Project, 1990; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 22)
  - "Sourcebook Capitol Hill Historic District Guidelines", 1990-1996; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 23)
  - Survey Costs and HI57 District Problems, 1995-1996; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 24)
  - Testimonies, 1986-1989; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 25)
  - "Tips from the Trade" Forum Plans and Organization Handouts, 1998 October; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 26)
  - Various Documents - minutes, agendas, notes, board information, 1988-1989; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 27)
  - Various Documents - minutes, agendas, and board information, 1989-1990; Series 19 (Box 167, Folder 28)